Hello hello hello friends how are you all
hopefully you will be very good friends today
I am going to share a very important thing with
you how to clean the festival team front
support you or any brother that is why
its tyre
companies different companies
give warranty for different time like
I bought 15 year old tyre from Europe and the tyre fitted on that side was from
Europe and it has a
warranty of three years for riding the bike
they reported that within six to seven months
some cracks started appearing in the tyre
and tracks started appearing so when I gave it for
servicing then it came to light that when
they washed the vehicle and
cleaned it properly then the first cracks that they felt were
not visible on it, only those
tracks which were missing were visible,
I will show you in the video oh
okay so later when the tyre was cleaned then
I came to know that cracks were completely visible on it
and how can this happen how can any tyre get damaged so quickly within 6 to 7 months so
then
I went to the company for servicing from where
Friends, sometimes we
often do this that during festivals
we directly approach the company,
but no, you should not do this.
First of all, you do not have to go to the dealer,
you should go to the company i.e. the place from where you purchased the vehicle. The
people there will inspect your tyre.
After inspecting the tyre, they will
make a letter and give it to you saying that we checked it and
it is defective like this, then they will recommend you
and after taking the tyre acceptance letter from there, you will
go to that tyre dealer.
You have taken the time of this company, then
they will be scared after hearing this. If you go to the
dealer of tyre robbers, then
you may have to face a lot of problems. They will
also trouble you
or not. This is like this, it is like that
in life. I am telling you my personal experience.
When I got the tyre letter made from here and took it to them, they
caught me,
inspected it and then said that yes, this
is a manufacturing defect because there are
two types of defects, one is a
manufacturing defect.  And the second one
is unconditional, if there are defects in it then
two types of guarantees are given in it, i.e.
quality and unconditional
warranty. In packing guarantee, that thing is covered
like if it starts rusting or if there is
some problem in the new time, then
all these things start forming in it, then it comes under
manufacturing quality.
In unconditional warranty, like if the tyre has
burst due to hitting something or has burst, then all
these things come under its control.
Many companies, looking at the unconditional body, considering
their credit, do
not bother you by showing them as correct. Some things are
replaced in the area and in a proper manner,
but some companies also bother you. So instead of
going directly to the oil dealer, first get the
vehicle
inspected at the place from where you purchased it, you will
get the letter. After reading that letter,
go to that dealer and tell him that we have got it
checked here and that recommendation letter is received.
When I went there, I got the
recommendation letter.  He
refused to give it to me and said that this is the weather in fact,
this is not a bad time, with respect, nothing has happened,
we cannot change it,
so I called him and showed him the photo,
I said look, it is lying correct in it
and it has been seven months since the car was parked
and you are saying that it is very fit, if there are as
many vehicles parked in front of your shop, then
tell me whether the weather is for my car or
for other vehicles, so when
I talked to him on a topical topic,
he started feeling that no friend,
now I will fall, so I said that I am
sitting in your car, then
where is your car parked, then I took his car and pointed towards the
comment, who said that there is no
side effect in your car,
then I am without recording, so when the
discussion took place like this, he agreed and even
after not agreeing, he said yes for one tile of
mine which was behind me
and said that it is okay and it will come in 108 stage,
we will replace you, so in this
way, I was retired in Europe and he
went there, so  Firstly they said that it will
cost 180 rupees and your tyre will be changed
and I also got a message of 100 rupees on my mobile
that it will be changed but when I went to get it
installed did you say that this is a
good quality tyre and a good quality tyre belonged to
my relative
but when they
replaced it they said that this is a tubeless tyre
and I will install it along with the tube it is of
good quality so I said ok no
problem you would have installed it so
they looked at it you can see the
text which I created exactly at the time
here and
here you can see the total 338 rupees plus
they said that it will cost me 100 rupees for this that
means a message came on 108 simple
they have taken 400 rupees 40 so I
understood that it is good
quality and we installed the tyre and tubeless tyre
earlier I had death voltage
so friends these things are understandable but
this thing is not that easy to get it changed,
you have to do it with full confidence
Talk to them, first of all people will try to
distract you by saying that it is like this and that and will
try to trouble you so that you go away
from there but if there is a
problem in your car, there is a problem in the tyre of your car, then it is there
because you are going there like this, then
you should
not reach there without any reason, you should
take a recommendation letter from the company so that they have to
replace it in any case, okay friends, so what
I was saying was that if there is really a
problem in the tyre, if it is cut or torn or it
comes under unconditional quality
or it
comes under manufacturing quality, then get it replaced because
it is related, then it is our right,
we can get it and should also get it, so
keep this thing in mind, so whenever you go,
talk to them with Providence and today
I introduced myself and
thank you so much, I hope that
all this
knowledge will be very helpful to all of you before getting the tyre changed and when you get it, then get
your letter made with that company and only after getting its recommendation letter
made, get it replaced.  I hope
you liked this video of mine,
thank you so much.